Interview with main voice actor
The Voice of Shana:
Kugimiya Rie
Tell us your opinion after reading the original Manga...
It has been terribly difficult.
Question:
About your image of Shana...
It's just an ordinary "fantasy" story, I thought.
If I don't read it... not reading it...
Wouldn't make a difference, or so I thought, but...
In the end, when I started working on it.
Thinking-it all over,
"I wondered about the feeling that before I know it"...
"The people I hold dear to my heart... like family...
Friends and such... suddenly all vanish out of existence..."
And then there was a lof of specific terms 1 didn't remember,
Maybe, knowing them I could convey great fear or sorrows...
Just reading-it, l forgot completely that the situations in there were made up.
And all these growing characters...
There were conflicts, there were drawbacks,...
There were fights, but...
Even with all that, as I thought, absolutely,
Nowhere a single line...
Well...
Felt like a somewhat "thin" shadow.
It may have felt so, but, we may say...
An everlasting... how to say... shadow", maybe.
Well, it has both the light and dark themes...
The story made progress very slowly...
Your impression when you first saw the preview.
Did you all saw it too?
Question:
Earlier I was shown the preview...
The preview was somehow really short, but...
It was like a movie and the soundtrack too was badass...
And even the animation was so great, l thought "it's somewhat REALLY good!", it really got into me.
The part they showed us was short, but extremely... The production world's view was so fixed...
That we told ourselves that’it.was really going to happen.
1 thought that, with this pace, the anime will do wonders...
It's giving me great hopes.
About Shana's image?
Question:
About Your View of Shana....
When I read the original story...
First, I thought she was extremely formidable, but...
She dealt with her so called "deep fears" fast, and...
All her fights till then, they were the proof of her very own existence...
Fighfing... was shaping the look on her face.
She interacted with the humans in various ways...
If you dig deep in to her soul, so to speak.
Yes, she was like saying "what's going to happen from now on?"
So...
She's a lively girl who is looking forward to whatever the future may bring.
That was my impression.
How did you interpret Shana?
When I held Shana's dialogue book in my hands....
Question:
When I did it for the very first time...
The sound technician told me that...
Good, do the voice acting as you're doing now, but lower the voice tone with a slightly lowered pitch...
When I changed my voice to match their suggestions...
I said: "No way! Shana can't sound like a kodomo", but...
we then went for that Minmin-like voice of Shana.
The mood in the anime fits the situation better that way.
It surpassed it, more than fit in that...
Stuff like Shana-chan's various emotions...
Deep fears...
I hope I expressed them with my heart in it...
About my rival...
Yoshida Kazumi-chan said...
When I've been reading the story, l kept saying to myself, "Kazumi-chan would be bad at this".
She is a lively woman who has lot of points concerning Shana and Yuuj's reality, but...
Stuff like Shana-chan's various emotions...
You know...
She seems so casual...
Shana is a like... she is so clever...
Combined with her ability to handle anything that happens.
Your message for the viewers.
Question:
The origindLstory is...
Extremely interesting, and'extremely complex, and...
The ones who ore fans of such complicated mysteries...
Honestly...
Really...
I wonder if there are many fans who get fascinated by a story such as this?
When I read this too, I loved it and it made me hold my breath...
Well...
Also for the fans of the light novel... hope I entertain them with my voice...
I too once read it, after all.
I'd be happy if the fans enjoy my voice.
| won't betray anyone's expectations, or else it would be like betraying the meaning in this.
1 think I have understood the whole story.
To me, the original story.has been interesting, and so,
I really wanted to dp all of it, but...
It seems the story is still progressing, so...
The light novel is the original work...
I wonder if the Anime can enjoy the same success.
We must live up to everyone's expectations, and if we able to, I'll be happy.
I voice Shana-chan very passionately.
Please cheer and support the author and the anime producers and the studio. Thank you.